Alex Beuscher

alexbeuscher@gmail.com 25 Glen Devin St. Amesbury, MA 01913 c: 617 359 - 6971

Overview

I have more than twenty years of experience working in marketing. I have originated digital campaigns, worked with stakeholders on high profile web properties, and managed several small teams to success. I also have experience as a storyteller, voice over artist, and video producer. I enjoy working with other people to create new and entertaining things - be they ad campaigns, products, or experiences.

Skills

Marketing SEO, Content Strategy, Analytics, Localization, Storytelling, Audio / Video production

Languages JavaScript, React, Node, HTML, CSS, GraphQL, GROQ, PHP

Applications 11ty, Marketo, ZenDesk, AWS Services, Git, Figma, Gatsby, Final Cut Pro, OneTrust,

Sanity.io, Contentstack, Wordpress, and others.

Experience

2020 - 2023 Senior Web Developer, Skydio, San Mateo, CA

Skydio.com's stack consists of Eleventy and Sanity.io. I managed several contractors in this role and worked with stakeholders to continuously improve the company's marketing site. I also assisted security with GDPR and CCPA compliance.

2019 –2021 Senior Web Developer & Team Lead, Contentstack, San Diego, CA

In this role I managed and mentored a team in Mumbai, India. The marketing and documentation sites were built using the company's headless CMS product along with Gatsby. I also provided voice over work and copy writing for their docs.

2017 -2020 Senior Web Developer, Dynamic Signal, San Bruno, CA

This was a remote position, working with Wordpress, ZenDesk, and Marketo on the company's web properties including their marketing and support sites. I also worked on the company's product docs and with their security team on compliance.

2013 - 2017 Senior Web Developer, 2K Games, Novato, CA

My role at 2K involved front and back end development on sites supporting our various game titles and other web properties. Security, localization, and usability were a primary focus. I also participated in regular security audits to ensure ongoing compliance with GDPR, CCPA, and additional security work due to the nature of the company's IP.

2008 -2011 Online Content Director, WAAF & Mike FM (Entercom), Allston, MA

At WAAF and Mike FM, I managed a team of content producers, and worked in a variety of roles to support and create video, web, and mobile content for our listeners in conjunction with our station's on-air personalities as well as local and national celebrities. I also supported our sales department by creating branding opportunities in our web promotions and linkage to on-air programming.

Education

BFA in Creative Writing, Emerson College